JIN KUAN MOO

Email: jkmoo0412@hotmail.com

Tel: 0892059402

LinkedIn URL: https://www.linkedin.com/in/jin-kuan-moo/

Profile Summary

I am a UCD Computer Science postgraduate who speaks fluent Chinese Mandarin, English, and Malay. I have full stack web development experience and project experience in SQL, Java, JavaScript, Python, AWS and machine learning. Besides that, I have great Data Analytics skills, Network & Internet layers knowledge(TCP/IP) as well as understanding of computer hardware architecture and OS (Windows, Linux). In terms of working experience, I had been a manufacturing manager in Krispy Kreme which involved monitoring a dedicated operation team of 20 members to deliver daily production. I also volunteered as an section leader in Code in Place hosted by Stanford University which conducts weekly online coding and Python lesson to a group of 15 students. I am confident that my extensive IT proficiency along with my great management and communication skills make me an strong candidate for the following position.

Education

Sep 2022 to Now MSc Computer Science in University College Dublin (UCD)

- Graduate in the end of 2023
- Completed Python, OOP, relational database & information system, web app development, operating system, and computational thinking, Java, Software Engineering, Data Structure, Computer Organization & Architecture, Network & Internet System, Data Analytics
- Currently working on a web application to predict the impact on urban flow for major events took place in Manhattan, New York. Technology stack includes React, Node, Express, Apache etc and machine learning algorithms like Random Forest and XGBoost etc.
- Cumulative Grade: first class-honour

Sep 2017 to May 2021 BSc Food Science in University College Dublin (UCD)

- ➤ Achieved first-class honour with an overall GPA of 3.77/4.2
- Good knowledge on food industry (technology, science, legislation)
- Familiar with HACCP, BRC, ISO, and experience in lab environment

Core Skills

- Good knowledge in Language such as HTML, CSS, Java, JavaScript, C++, Python
- Frontend tools: Rest API, React JS, TypeScript
- Backend tools: MySQL, Flask, AWS RDS, Node.js, Express.js
- ➤ Data Analytics skills (CRISP-DM), machine learning skills(scikit-learn), Modelling such as Linear Regression, Logistic Regression, Random Forest, XGBoost etc.
- JavaFX, Scene Builder
- Familiar with hardware structure of computer and Network & Internet layers knowledge (TCP/IP)
- Operating systems such as Windows, Linux as well as the use of VM (AWS EC2)
- > Data Structures and Algorithms, OOP, Full stack web development
- Great Microsoft Office and Git(GitHub) skills
- Experience with Anacondas, Jupyter Notebooks, Eclipse, VSCode
- Experience on handling JSON, CSV, and other file formats
- Experience with agile methodologies
- Fluent in Chinese and English with basic knowledge in Malay

Volunteer

Apr 2023 to Jun 2023 Section Leader in Code In Place, Stanford University

- Conducts a weekly online coding lesson to a group of 15 students from all around the world
- Mainly covers the material from famous Stanford CS106A modules, including basic Python, console Programming, Graphic Programming etc.
- Refining teaching and communication abilities while actively engaging with students, helping them in enhancing their coding skills and proficiency

Portfolio

- > A python project that recommends the closest restaurant with the highest rating based on location of user
- A RPG game that mimics a battle between enemies and allies with a controllable character that can cast different action based on user input
- A project using JavaScript, JSON, HTML, and CSS that performs filter and search functions on a list of US senators with detailed information
- Personal blog
- ➤ Data analytics project using CRISP-DM on COVID-19 data from CDC, data cleaning and preparation, prediction modelling (linear regression, logistic regression, random forest), and optimisation
- Classic video game "Asteroids" based on java and javaFX
- A full stack web application that displays occupancy and weather information for Dublin Bikes using AWS, Python, JavaScript, Flask, Nginx, Gunicorn along with machine learning for prediction

Working Experience

Sept 2021 to Jun 2022

Manufacturing Manager in Krispy Kreme

- Supervise a dedicated operations team to ensure that all safety, quality, and legal standards are maintained
- Keep track of inventory control, yield record, safety compliance, and traceability documentations
- > Good expertise in machines such as extruder, Magna Mixer, Groen Kettle, Proofer etc.
- > Use Reflex Planning to generate daily planner and build and making necessary amendments

May 2020 to Sep 2020

Intern in Safco Fine Foods

- Working as Intern (Including goods-in, preparation, cooking, and packaging)
- > Keeping HACCP, traceability, and other relevant documentations in record
- Doing R&D on vegan cheese

Achievement & Certificate

- Four-years holder of UCD Global Southeast Excellent Scholarship
- ➤ Holder of UCD Food Science Stage 2 and 3 Scholarship
- Recipient of Kepak Best in Class Award: Food Science in UCD
- School representative of Exchange programme to Cornell University, US
- ➤ Google IT Support Professional Certificate
- Udemy Guide to Cyber Security Certificate